Guide to the Walter De la Mare Papers, 1912-1984
Department of Special Collections
- Miscellaneous
  - Xerox of entry on Naomi Royde Smith. Catholic Authors. ed. Matthew Hoehn. 1952.p. 542-4. With cover letter to Dorothy Hatch from Joseph Agolia, dated July 23, 1984. (Box 9)
  - Flyer for exhibit entitled Hofstra - The History of a University. 1979. (Box 9)
  - Flyer for The Thirties in England. New York Public Library. 1979. (Box 9)
  - Paper bookmark. Dancing Hours. Fogg Art Museum, Harvard University. (Box 9)
  - A Local Habitation and a Name. The Imprint of the Stanford Libraries Associates. October, 1979.By Dorothy Hatch. (Box 9)
  - The Leaden Bells of Modern Poetry. Lord Dunsany. The Saturday Review. February 6, 1954. (Box 9)
  - Xerox of program from Rugby School of the Rupert Brooke Memorial. March 28, 1919. (Box 9)
  - Xerox of program from Rugby School Chapel of the Unveiling of the Portrait Medallion of Rupert Brooke. March 28, 1919. (Box 9)
- Scores by various composers with words and poetry by Walter de la Mare:, Accession 1993-101
  - 1. Rachel, n.d. (Box 10)
  - 2. Three songs from Dune-home, inscribed, 1922. (Box 10)
  - 3. The road of evening, inscribed, n.d. (Box 10)
  - 4. Bluebells, n.d. (Box 10)
  - 5. Invocation, 1968. (Box 10)
  - 6. Someone came knocking, inscribed, 1923. (Box 10)
  - 7. A song of enchantment, 1922. (Box 10)
  - 8. Songs, 1916. (Box 10)
  - 9. Autumn,1933. (Box 10)
  - 10. Portraits, 1919. (Box 10)
  - 11. An epitaph, 1922. (Box 10)
  - 12. Three songs, 1923. (Box 10)
  - 13. Four songs, 1923. (Box 10)
  - 14. Musings, n.d. (Box 10)
  - 15. To daffodils, 1927. (Box 10)
  - 16. Dubbuldideery, n.d. (Box 10)
  - 17. She's me forgot, n.d. (Box 10)
  - 18. The galliass, n.d. (Box 10)
  - 19-20. Nevermore, sailor, 1925, (2 copies) (Box 10)
  - 21. The unchanging, 1926. (Box 10)
  - 22. Earth folk, 1923. (Box 10)
  - 23. Nod, 1927. (Box 10)
  - 24. Silver, 1933. (Box 10)
  - 25. Someone, 1923. (Box 10)
  - 26. The three cherry trees, 1925. (Box 10)
  - 27. Songs (12), inscribed, 1916. (Box 10)
  - 28. Songs (8), inscribed, 1916. (Box 10)